Guide to the Emilie F. Miller papers, 1987-1991
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
  - New Initiative Services Implementation- Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse Services, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - New Imitative Services Implementation- Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse Services, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Coalition- Public Hearing Schedule License Regulation Revision, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia- Actual Fiscal Revenues, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia- Correspondence, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia- Disability Related Bills, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia- Operational Details and Coalition, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1989 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia/ Alliance for the Mentally Ill, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Addresses, Cards, and Phone Messages, 1991-1993 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Resume, May 25, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Announcement of Candidacy for Re-election, circa 1991 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Commission on the University in the 20th Century, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Autographed Program- Signed by Birch Bayh, June 24, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Clozaril (Clozapine)- New Hope for Schizophrenic Patients 1, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Clozaril (Clozapine)- New Hope for Schizophrenic Patients 2, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Clozaril (Clozapine)- New Hope for Schizophrenic Patients 3, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Clozaril (Clozapine)- New Hope for Schizophrenic Patients 4, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Membership, 1989-1992 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Robb, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Alumni Review Sesquicentennial Edition, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Military Institute Letter, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    Originally in Virginia Military Institute book "The Spirit"
  - Women, Black, and Hispanic State Elected Leaders, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Center of the American Woman in Politics Forum for State Legislators, November 14-17, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - 1987 Campaign Letters, Pamphlets, and Information (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Public School Alternative, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Forum! Program 343- Junior Achievement, 1980s-1990s (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Emilie Miller for State Senate "No Choice" Radio- audio cassette tape, October 29, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Emilie Miller for State Senate "No Choice" Radio- audio cassette tape, October 29, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Emilie Miller- Virginia Military Institute- Channel 56 video cassette tape, 1990s (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - CNN Crossfire Appearance- video cassette tape, April 8, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Koppel Show Appearance- Virginia Military Institute video cassette tape, 1990s (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Emilie Miller- Virginia Military Institute- Channel 56 DVD copy of video cassette tape, 1990s (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - CNN Crossfire Appearance- DVD copy video cassette tape, 1990s (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Koppel Show Appearance- Virginia Military Institute- DVD copy of video cassette tape, 1990s (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - 1988 Women's Democratic Convention Women's Agenda flyer, June 3, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - 1988 Women's Democratic Convention Women's Agenda flyer, June 3, 19888 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 216- Women's History Month in Virginia framed copy, February 1991 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - State Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services Board Community Leadership Award-framed, January 27, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 4)